CV

Personal information

First name: Hayk

Last name: Dallakyan

Phone number: (041) 575 - 777

E-mail address: dallakyanhayk@gmail.com

Experience

05/2020 - NowMiddle-Senior (then Team lead) Full Stack Developer at BeeWeb company (MERN)

05/2016 - 05/2020 Middle-Senior web developer at Best Soft CJSC company (PHP)

10/2015 - 05/2016 Middle web developer at Studio One company (PHP)

04/2015 - 08/2015 Junior web developer at Iguan System company (PHP)

02/2015 - 03/2015 Junior web developer at IT park (PHP)

Education

2010-2012 Masters degree in Geology faculty, at Yerevan

State University

2004-2008 Bachelor's degree in Geology faculty, at Yerevan

State University

Certificates

• Cybersecurity Essential, got certificate from Cisco https://www.credly.com/badges/73909a13-5cf1-4aa2-b0be-f7461a07562c/public_url

Skills

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript
- Jquery
- React / Redux / Flux
- ExpressJS, NodeJS
- Mongodb (aggregation)
- Android development with HTML,CSS,JavaScript
- Cordova
- PHP
- PHP OOP
- Smarty: PHP Template Engine
- CodeIgniter
- MySQL
- PDO

Languages

- Armenian Native
- Russian Conversational
- English Conversational

About me

Since 2015 I started work as a web developer. I worked as a PHP developer until May 2020. I studied and worked with JQuery, PHP, PHP

OOP, Zend, Smarty, MySQL, SQL, PDO. From May 2016 to May 2020 I worked on programs for internal document system management. My knowledge of database architecture and database design is very well. I can build websites, also document management systems. Since May 2020 I started work as a Senior MERN stack developer. Now in MERN, my experience is for about 3 years. In 2022 I studied Cybersecurity Essential and got a certificate. I'm interested in cybersecurity, and I would like to get start in cybersecurity. I specialize in development, but I'm sure, I can be very well in cybersecurity. I can do also both web development and cybersecurity, if it's possible.